A Guide to the Rockefeller Brothers Fund records, Awards in Arts Education Program, RG 7 FA776
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Administration
  - Office Files
    - Recommendation Letters Supporting Non-Finalist Schools - 1983-1984 (Box 34, Folder 301)
    - Good Support Letters from Non-Finalist Schools - Year Three, 1983 (Box 35, Folder 302)
    - Letters from Schools That Were Rejected, 1981-1982 (Box 35, Folder 303-304)
    - RBF Education Resources Group, 1981-1982, 1985 (Box 35, Folder 305)
    - National School Boards Association, 1983, 1984, 1988 (Box 35, Folder 306)
    - National Association of Elementary School Principals, 1980-1983 (Box 35, Folder 307)
    - Reactions to Arts Awards Program, 1981-1982 (Box 35, Folder 308)
    - Committee Suggestions/Comments, 1981-1984 (Box 35, Folder 309)
    - Patricia Peterson, 1983-1984 (Box 35, Folder 310)
    - Howard Gardner, 1980-1983, 1985 (Box 35, Folder 311)
    - David Rockefeller, Jr., 1981-1985 (Box 35, Folder 312)
    - Molly LaBerge, 1981-1985 (Box 35, Folder 313)
    - Margo Albert, 1981-1982 (Box 35, Folder 314)
    - Martin Engel, 1974, 1976, 1979-1984 (Box 35, Folder 315)
    - Barbara Carlisle, 1980, 1983-1984 (Box 36, Folder 316)
    - Rosann Cox, 1984, no date (Box 36, Folder 317)
    - Donis Dondis, 1982, 1984 (Box 36, Folder 318)
    - John Mahlmann, 1981-1983 (Box 36, Folder 319)
    - Jon Murray, 1983 (Box 36, Folder 320)
    - Anne Taylor, 1981-1983 (Box 36, Folder 321)
    - Betty Blayton Taylor, 1980, 1983, no date (Box 36, Folder 322)
    - Mary Jo Thompson, 1984 (Box 36, Folder 323)
    - Rosemarie Cook, 1983-1985 (Box 36, Folder 324)
    - Bennett Reimer, 1980, 1982-1984, 1989, no date (Box 36, Folder 325)
    - "The Magenta Bowling Ball" by William Matthews, 1984 (Box 36, Folder 326)
    - "A Week at Music-and-Art" by Sharon Olds, 1984 (Box 36, Folder 327)
    - "Learning It and Loving It in Houston" by Cheryl Crooks, no date (Box 36, Folder 328)
    - "The Luck of Farragut High School" by Dave Smith, no date (Box 36, Folder 329)
    - "Making Art at Elkhart: the 3 R's" by Carol Muske, 1983 (Box 36, Folder 330)
    - "The kids come by on bicycles..." by Robert Hass, 1984 (Box 36, Folder 331)
    - Draft: "A Report on the RBF Awards in Arts Education Program", Lonna Jones, editor, 1989 July; Folders 336-339, 2nd copy of Report (Box 36, Folder 332-334, Box 37, Folder 335-339)
    - Brochures - Years 1 through 4, 1981-1984 (Box 37, Folder 340)
- Applications
  Series 3, Applications, is the largest of the three series and demonstrates the popularity of the Awards program based on the sheer number of applications received.
  - Applications Dated 1981 for Year 1 (1982)
    - Alabama, 1981 (Box 37, Folder 341)
      Including: Julian Newman Elementary School.
    - Alaska, 1981 (Box 37, Folder 342)
      Including: Austin E. Lathrop High School.
    - Arizona, 1981 (Box 37, Folder 343-345)
      Including: Alma Elementary, Desert Sands Junior High, Holladay Intermediate Magnet.
    - Arkansas, 1981 (Box 37, Folder 346-347)
      Including: Cabot Junior and Cabot Middle, Jonesboro Public Schools.
    - California, 1981 (Box 37, Folder 348-354, Box 38, Folder 355-384, Box 39, Folder 385-401)
      Including: Armijo High, Arroyo Seco Junior High, Berendo Junior High, Berkeley High, Buford Elementary, Camino Pablo Elementary, Caroldale Avenue Elementary, Chico Senior High, Chula Vista High, Del Mar Heights Elementary, Mary A. Deterding Elementary, Eagle Rock High, Benjamin Franklin Middle, Guerneville, Hillcrest Center for Enriched Studies, Hollywood High, Robert F. Kennedy Elementary, Thomas Starr King Junior High, James Logan High, Lorena Street Elementary, Lorenzo Manor Elementary, Lowell High, Marina Middle, John Marshall High, Micheltorena Street Elementary, Monroe Elementary, Mountain View Elementary, Mt. Carmel High, Multnomah Street Elementary, New Traditions Elementary, Oakdale Elementary, Ohlone Elementary, Orosi High, Padan Elementary, Palisades High, Ponderosa Elementary, Rancho Cordova Elementary, Theodore Roosevelt High, Sacramento High, San Dimas High, San Mateo High, Santa Cruz High, Saratoga Elementary, Sonoma Valley Unified School District: Dunbar Elementary, Sonora High, John Swett Alternative, Tamalpais High, Marjorie H. Tobias Elementary, Twin Hills Union School District, University High, Vintage High, Wright Elementary School District.
      - Guide to slides R-1 to R-51 - Program Examples, 2016:FA776:070 (Box 37, Folder 354)
    - Colorado, 1981 (Box 39, Folder 402-406)
      Including: Dry Creek Elementary, Grant Elementary, General William Mitchell High, Queen Palmer Elementary, Steele Elementary.
    - Connecticut, 1981 (Box 39, Folder 407-414)
      Including: Duffy Elementary, Timothy Dwight Elementary, Greenwich High, Illing Junior High, Sage Park Junior High, Staples High, Willington Public Schools, Windham High.
    - District of Columbia (Box 39, Folder 415)
      Including: Duke Ellington School of the Arts
    - Florida, 1981 (Box 39, Folder 416-422)
      Including: William R. Boone High, Catalina Elementary, Coral Springs High, Lake Como Elementary, John Love Elementary, Pinellas Park Senior High, William M. Raines Senior High.
    - Georgia, 1981 (Box 39, Folder 423-424)
      Including: Irwin County Elementary, Union County High.
    - Idaho, 1981 (Box 39, Folder 425)
      Including: Dalton Gardens Elementary.
    - Illinois, 1981 (Box 39, Folder 426, Box 40, Folder 427-440)
      Including: Chippewa Elementary, Edwardsville High, Forest Park Public Schools, Franklin Fine Arts Center, Friends of Oscar Mayer School, Glencoe Public Schools, Lincoln Park High, Lyons Township High, Owen Marsh Elementary, Niles Township High - West Division, Oak Park and River Forest High, James Whitcomb Riley High, South Shore High, SPEED Developmental Center, Booker T. Washington Elementary.
    - Indiana, 1981 (Box 40, Folder 441-447)
      Including: Arlington High, Duneland School Corporation, Indiana Coalition of Elementary School Principals, Memorial Park Middle, North Central High, North Vermillion Junior-Senior High, Tolleston Middle.
    - Iowa, 1981 (Box 40, Folder 448-449)
      Including: Anamosa Community School District, Harding Junior High.
    - Kansas, 1981 (Box 40, Folder 450)
      Including: Isely Elementary School: Isely Creative Center.
    - Kentucky, 1981 (Box 40, Folder 451-455)
      Including: J. Graham Brown School, Gavin Cochran Elementary, Hardin County Schools, Iroquois High, Samuel V. Noe Middle.
    - Louisiana, 1981 (Box 41, Folder 456-467)
      Including: Audubon Elementary, C. E. Byrd High, Lusher Alternative Elementary, McDonogh 15 Elementary, McDonogh No. 39 Elementary, New Orleans Center for Creative Arts, A. A. Songy, Sr. Elementary, Southwood High.
    - Maryland, 1981 (Box 42, Folder 468-483)
      Including: Baltimore School for the Arts, Centennial High, Clarksburg Elementary, Clemens Crossing Elementary, DuFief Elementary, Dulaney Senior High, Faulkner Ridge Elementary, Governor Thomas Johnson High, Walter Johnson High, Old Mill Senior High, Olney Elementary, Seneca Valley High, Seven Locks Elementary, Severna Park Senior High, Walt Whitman High, Thomas S. Wootton High.
    - Massachusetts, 1981 (Box 42, Folder 484-498)
      Including: Agawam High, Barnstable High, Burlington High, William N. DeBerry School, East Falmouth Elementary, East Somerville Community School, English High, R. Stewart Esten School, Hyman Fine Elementary, Glover and Eveleth School District, Monument Mount Regional High, James Otis School, Hill Roberts Elementary, Walpole Senior High, Wellesley Public Schools.
    - Michigan, 1981 (Box 42, Folder 499-517)
      Including: Averill Elementary, Cass Technical High, City High, East Detroit High, Eisenhower High, Edsel Ford High, P. D. Graham Elementary, Harlan Elementary, Hillsdale Community Schools, Kalamazoo Central High/Loy Norrix High, Ivan Luddington Middle, Miami and Huron Elementary Schools, North Muskegon Public School District, Okemos High/Kinawa Middle, Parkview Elementary-Eaton County Intermediate School District, Pierce Community School, Summerfield Community School, Traverse City Senior High, Waverly Elementary Schools.
    - Minnesota, 1981 (Box 42, Folder 518-520, Box 43, Folder 521-529)
      Including: Hans Christian Anderson Elementary, Lincoln Senior High, Lowell Elementary, Marcy/Holmes Open School, Marietta-Nassau School, Alexander Ramsey High, St. Paul Central High, Scenic Heights Elementary, Webster Magnet School.
    - Mississippi, 1981 (Box 43, Folder 530-533)
      Including: Columbia Public Schools, McComb High, Meridian High-North Campus, Warren Central Junior High.
    - Missouri, 1981 (Box 43, Folder 534-540)
      Including: Affton High, Hickman Mills High, Honors Art Program-St. Louis Public Schools, Marshall High, Sycamore Hills Elementary, Valley Park Elementary, Mary Harmon Weeks School.
    - Montana, 1981 (Box 43, Folder 541)
      Including: Box Elder High.
    - Nebraska, 1981 (Box 43, Folder 542)
      Including: Dundee Elementary.
    - Nevada, 1981 (Box 43, Folder 543)
      Including: Elko Junior-Senior High.
    - New Hampshire, 1981 (Box 43, Folder 544-545, Box 44, Folder 546-547)
      Including: New Durham School, Bernice A. Ray Elementary.
    - New Jersey, 1981 (Box 44, Folder 548-569)
      Including: Bergenfield High, Cleveland Elementary, Conover Road School, Alice Costello Elementary, Crim Elementary, Fieldstone Elementary, Grant School, Hillside School, Holdrum Middle, Jefferson School, Lenox Elementary, Lincoln Elementary, Matawan Regional High, Middlesex County Adjunct High School of the Arts, Moonachie Public Schools-Robert L. Craig Elementary, Dwight Morrow High, Northern Valley Regional High, Orange High, Princeton High, South Brunswick High, Summit High, Washington Park School.
    - New Mexico, 1981 (Box 44, Folder 570-571)
      Including: Gadsden Independent School District, Kennedy Middle.
    - New York, 1981 (Box 44, Folder 572-585, Box 45, Folder 586-628, Box 46, Folder 629-646)
      Including: Allegany Central School, Arlington Middle, Caroline G. Atkinson School, Baldwinsville Central School District-L. Pearl Palmer Elementary, Bilingual-Bicultural Arts School, Briarcliff Road School, City Honors School, Marie Curie Junior High, Dutch Broadway School, Emerson School, Greenfield School, Guilderland High, Harbor Junior High for the Performing Arts-Boys Harbor, Inc., Hartford Central School, High School of Art and Design, Hudson City School District, Hunter College Elementary, Intermediate School 70, Intermediate School 292, Jamestown High, John F. Kennedy School, Meyer Levin Junior High, Longfellow Middle, Lynbrook South Middle, Mamaroneck High, Mark Twain Junior High, Midland School, George W. Miller Elementary, Minetto Elementary, Andrew Muller Primary, Nanuet Public Schools-A. MacArthur Barr Middle, Narrowsburg Central School, Lewiston Porter North Elementary, North Rose-Wolcott Central School, William Nottingham High, P. S. 17-LaSalle Junior High-Manhattan, P. S. 31-The Bayside School-Queens, P. S. 40-Manhattan, P. S. 59-The Beekman School-Manhattan, P. S. 75-Emily Dickinson Elementary-Manhattan, P. S. 84-The Sol Bloom School-Manhattan, P. S. 96-Bronx, P. S. 107-Queens, P. S. 107-The John W. Kimball Learning Center-Brooklyn, P. S. 112-Bronx, P. S. 125-Ralph Bunche School-Manhattan, P. S. 152-Glenwood Road School-Brooklyn, P. S. 167-Wagner Junior High-Manhattan, P. S. 183-Queens, P. S. 184-Flushing Manor School-Queens, P. S. 189-Manhattan, P. S. 192-Brooklyn, P. S. 193-The Alfred J. Kennedy School-Queens, P. S. 272K-Brooklyn, P. S. 312-Brooklyn, Satellite East Junior High, Schodack Central School District, Shorackappock Elementary, Special Primary School 31, Bronx-William Lloyd Garrison, Sugar Loaf Union Free School District, R. L. Thomas High, South Shore High, The Vleigh School-Public School 165-Queens, Wantagh Elementary, William B. Ward Elementary, Waterford-Half Moon Elementary, Webster Elementary, Weedsport Central School System, White Plains Intermediate, Daniel Hale Williams School-I. S. 180-Bronx.
      - Andrew Muller Primary School, Lower Rocky Point Road, Miller Place, NY 11764, (516) 473-0123, 2016:FA776:071 (Box 45, Folder 603)
    - North Carolina, 1981 (Box 46, Folder 647-653)
      Including: Glenn Junior High, Myers Park High, Walter Hines Page Senior High, Shelby High, Skyland Intermediate, Southern Middle, South Park High.
    - North Dakota, 1981 (Box 47, Folder 654-655)
      Including: Fargo Public Schools.
    - Ohio, 1981 (Box 47, Folder 656-664)
      Including: Albany Elementary, Etna Elementary, Fifth Street School, Jackson-Milton Local School District, Kemp Elementary, Pleasant Local Schools, School for Creative and Performing Arts, Warren Local School District, Woodrow Wilson Elementary.
    - Oklahoma, 1981 (Box 47, Folder 665-667)
      Including: Ardmore Middle, Dwight D. Eisenhower Elementary, Wiley Post Elementary.
    - Oregon, 1981 (Box 47, Folder 668-671)
      Including: Sam Barlow High, Jefferson High, Magnet Arts School, Oakland High.
    - Pennsylvania, 1981 (Box 47, Folder 672-677, Box 48, Folder 678-691)
      Including: Allerdice High, Clarion Area Junior-Senior High, Dible Elementary, Forest Hills Elementary, Fountain Hill Elementary, Samuel Gompers Center for Expressive Arts, Harrisburg Arts Magnet School, Hazleton Area School District, High School for Performing and Creative Arts, Johnsonburg Elementary, John Paul Jones Junior High, General McLane High, North Hills High, Palmyra Area High, Robert Blair Pollock Elementary, Rogers School for Creative and Performing Arts, Tamanend Junior High, Tawanka and Poquessing Elementary Schools, Williamsport Area High.
    - Rhode Island, 1981 (Box 48, Folder 692-695)
      Including: Cranston Public Schools, Cumberland High, Fairlawn Lincoln Elementary, Woonsocket Senior High.
      - Creative Dance, Cranston Public Schools, 2016:FA776:072 (Box 48, Folder 692)
    - South Carolina, 1981 (Box 48, Folder 696-701)
      Including: Airport High, Mary Ford Elementary, Greenville County Fine Arts Center, Laurens District 55 High, Rock Hill High, Spartanburg High.
    - Tennessee, 1981 (Box 48, Folder 702-705)
      Including: Cleveland Junior High, Crossville Elementary, Rozelle Elementary, White County High.
    - Texas, 1981 (Box 48, Folder 706-710, Box 49, Folder 711-714)
      Including: L. C. Anderson High, Bonham Middle, Eugene Field Elementary, Lyndon Baines Johnson High, Robert E. Lee Elementary, Longfellow Elementary, Roscoe High, Slaton Junior High, Western Hills High No. 268.
    - Utah, 1981 (Box 49, Folder 715-716)
      Including: Mountview Elementary, Panguitch Elementary-Integrated Arts Program-Title IV-C.
    - Vermont, 1981 (Box 49, Folder 717-718)
      Including: Mt. Abraham Union High, Vermont Achievement Center.
    - Virginia, 1981 (Box 49, Folder 719-728)
      Including: Bellevue Model School, John B. Cary Model School, Clover Hill High, Falls Church City Elementary Schools-Mount Daniel and Thomas Jefferson, Grafton Village Elementary, Lexington High, Newport News Public Schools, Plaza Junior High, Tabb High, Woodville Elementary-"Arts on the Hill".
    - Washington, 1981 (Box 49, Folder 729-735)
      Including: Bothell High, Kamiakin Junior High, Orcas Island School District, Taholah School District.
    - West Virginia, 1981 (Box 49, Folder 736-740, Box 50, Folder 741-746)
      Including: Cameron Elementary, Clay County High, Gilmer County High, Liberty High, Moorefield Elementary, New Martinsville School, Parkersburg High, Princeton High, University High, Washington Irving High, Woodrow Wilson High.
    - Wisconsin, 1981 (Box 50, Folder 747-749)
      Including: Elm Creative Arts School, Lincoln High, Marinette Middle.
  - Applications Dated 1982 for Year 2 (1983)
    - Alabama, 1981 (Box 50, Folder 750-751)
      Including: Alabama School of Fine Arts, Ramsay Alternative High.
    - Arizona, 1981 (Box 50, Folder 752-758)
      Including: L. W. Cross Junior High, Desert Winds Elementary, John Jacobs Elementary, Miller Valley School, Sacaton Middle, Show Low Junior High, Lulu Walker Elementary.
    - California, 1981 (Box 50, Folder 759-776)
      Including: Arts School, Buford Elementary, Dr. William L. Cobb Elementary, Cupertino Union School District, Mary A. Deterding Elementary, El Modena High, Grant School, Jacoby Creek School, Linda Vista Primary/Longfellow Elementary-Joint Application, Los Feliz Elementary, Magnolia Elementary, John Marshall Elementary, Murray Junior High, O'Farrell School of Creative and Performing Arts, Point Vicinte Elementary, Santa Monica High, Solana Vista-Skyline School, Neomia B. Willmore Elementary.
    - Colorado, 1981 (Box 51, Folder 777)
      Including: Heritage Elementary.
    - Connecticut, 1982 (Box 51, Folder 778-780)
      Including: Enrico Hermi High, A. Ward Spaulding School, Westover Elementary.
    - Delaware, 1982 (Box 51, Folder 781)
      Including: Delcastle Technical High.
    - Georgia, 1982 (Box 51, Folder 782-784)
      Including: Bremen High, Fayette County High, Lake Park Elementary.
    - Idaho, 1982 (Box 51, Folder 785)
      Including: Mountain Home High.
    - Illinois, 1982 (Box 51, Folder 786-792)
      Including: Arts in Basic Education-Charleston Elementary Schools, Andrew Cooke Magnet School, Deerfield High, Forest View High, Lyons Township High, Proviso East High, Willowbrook High.
    - Indiana, 1982 (Box 51, Folder 793)
      Including: West Lafayette High.
    - Iowa, 1982 (Box 51, Folder 794)
      Including: Clinton High.
    - Kentucky, 1982 (Box 51, Folder 795-796)
      Including: Hardin County Educational Television, Model Laboratory School.
    - Louisiana, 1982 (Box 51, Folder 797-800)
      Including: Audubon Elementary, Livingston Middle, McDonogh 15 Elementary, New Orleans Center for Creative Arts.
    - Maine, 1982 (Box 51, Folder 801-802)
      Including: Orland Consolidated School, Rangeley Lakes Regional School.
    - Maryland, 1982 (Box 51, Folder 803-805)
      Including: Olney Elementary, William T. Page Elementary, Walbrook Senior High.
    - Massachusetts, 1982 (Box 52, Folder 805A-811)
      Including: Agassiz Elementary, Arlington Junior High East, Fort River School, Hopedale Junior-Senior High, McCarthy-Towne Elementary, Project Reach-Randolph Public Schools, Wellesley Junior High-Middle School.
    - Michigan, 1982 (Box 52, Folder 812-818)
      Including: Averill Elementary, Center for the Arts and Sciences, Community High, Mackinaw Middle, Pierce Creative Arts Community School, Upton Elementary, Winans Elementary.
    - Minnesota, 1982 (Box 52, Folder 819-826)
      Including: Central Performing Arts-Central High, Chisago Lakes Senior High, Laporte High, Long Prairie High, Hubert Olson Junior High, Orono Independent School District 278, Alexander Ramsey High, Webster Magnet School.
    - Mississippi, 1982 (Box 52, Folder 827-828)
      Including: Moss Point High, South Natchez-Adams High.
    - Missouri, 1982 (Box 52, Folder 829-831)
      Including: Honors Art Program-St. Louis Public Schools, Ravenwood Elementary, Mary Harmon Weeks Elementary.
    - Montana, 1982 (Box 52, Folder 832)
      Including: Hellgate Elementary.
    - Nebraska, 1982 (Box 52, Folder 833-834)
      Including: Grand Island High, Waterloo Public School.
    - New Hampshire, 1982 (Box 52, Folder 835)
      Including: Concord High.
    - New Jersey, 1982 (Box 52, Folder 836-848)
      Including: F. M. Gaudineer Middle, Glen Rock Junior-Senior High, Harrison Township School, Hasbrouck Heights High, Irvington High, Morris County Vocational-Technical School, North Huterdon Regional High School District, Perth Amboy High, Princeton High, Roosevelt Public School, Vroom Learning Center, Westville Public Schools, Whittier School.
    - New York, 1982 (Box 53, Folder 849-873)
      Including: Andover Central School, Louis Armstrong Middle-I. S. 227Q, Simon Baruch Junior High-J. H. S. 104M, Buffalo Academy for Visual and Performing Arts, City Honors School, Columbus Avenue School, Community School 61, John Dewey High, East Harlem Performing Arts School, East Islip High, Jacob Gunther School-North Bellmore Elementary Schools, Harbor Junior High of the Performing Arts, Herricks High, I. S. 44, Irvington High, J. H. S. 56-Corlears Junior High, Lindenhurst Public Schools, Longfellow Middle, William Nottingham Senior High, P. S. 113Q, Ridge Street School/Blind Brook High, School of the Arts at Monroe, Adlai E. Stevenson High, Vestal Central School District, Walton High.
    - Ohio, 1982 (Box 53, Folder 874-878)
      Including: Fort Hayes Career Center, Jackson-Milton Middle, Mansfield City Schools, Pike Delta York High, Warren High and Barlow-Vincent Elementary.
    - Oklahoma, 1982 (Box 53, Folder 879-880)
      Including: Eisenhower Elementary, Wiley Post Elementary.
    - Oregon, 1982 (Box 53, Folder 881-882)
      Including: Crater High, Magnet Arts School.
    - Pennsylvania, 1982 (Box 53, Folder 883-893)
      Including: Carmichaels Area Elementary Schools, Central Bucks High-East, Easterly Parkway Elementary, Forest Hills Elementary, Harrisburg Arts Magnet School, High School for Creative and Performing Arts, Margaret Milliones Middle, Willam Penn High, Penn-Trafford High, Scenic Hills Elementary, Tawanka Elementary.
    - Rhode Island, 1982 (Box 54, Folder 894)
      Including: West Warwick Senior High.
    - South Carolina, 1982 (Box 54, Folder 895-896)
      Including: Laurens District 55 High, Northwood Middle.
    - Tennessee, 1982 (Box 54, Folder 897-898)
      Including: Big Ridge Elementary, Farragut High.
    - Texas, 1982 (Box 54, Folder 899-904)
      Including: Aldine Contemporary Education Center, Bowie High, Edinburg High, A. Davis Ford Elementary, Gregory-Lincoln Education Center, Sidney Lanier Vanguard for the Expressive Arts.
    - Vermont, 1982 (Box 54, Folder 905-907)
      Including: Peoples Academy, State Street School, Union-32 High.
    - Virgin Islands, 1982 (Box 54, Folder 908)
      Including: Charlotte Amalie High.
    - Virginia, 1982 (Box 54, Folder 909-915)
      Including: W. C. Bryant Intermediate, Bush Hill Elementary, Lexington High, Sherwood Forest Elementary, Springfield Estates Elementary, J. E. B. Stuart High, West Springfield High.
    - Washington, 1982 (Box 54, Folder 916)
      Including: Shorewood High.
    - West Virginia, 1982 (Box 54, Folder 917)
      Including: Scarbo Elementary.
    - Wisconsin, 1982 (Box 54, Folder 918-921)
      Including: Elm Creative Arts School, Marinette Middle, Oak Creek Senior High, Sauk Prairie Middle.
  - Applications Dated 1983 for Year 3 (1984)
    - Alabama, 1983 (Box 54, Folder 922-926)
      Including: Alabama School of Fine Arts, George Washington Carver High, Ramsay Alternative High.
    - Arizona, 1983 (Box 55, Folder 927-937)
      Including: Carillo Intermediate, Corona Del Sol High, Elbert A. Gump School, Hollinger Elementary, Manzanita Elementary, Myers Elementary, Orange Grove Junior High, Santa Rita High, Seven-Mile Elementary, Tanque Verde Elementary, Utterback Junior High.
    - Arkansas, 1983 (Box 55, Folder 938-940)
      Including: College Station Kindergarten, Dardanelle Middle, Van Buren High.
    - California, 1983 (Box 55, Folder 941-956)
      Including: Angeles Mesa Elementary, Centinela Valley Consortium for the Arts-Juan de Anza, Cerritos Elementary, Henry T. Gage Junior High, Miguel Leonis High, Loyola Village Fine and Performing Arts Magnet Center, Magnolia Junior High, Martinez Junior High, Ninety-Second Street School, School for Creative and Performing Arts, Robert Louis Stevenson School, Tamalpais High, Third Street Elementary, Vista High, Walnut High, Wilsona Elementary.
    - Colorado, 1983 (Box 55, Folder 957-959)
      Including: Cherry Creek High, Rocky Mountain High, Timnath Elementary.
    - Connecticut, 1983 (Box 55, Folder 960-966)